Hello! This is Honoka Akimoto of Super Turn Strong Energy Positive Exciting Soulful ROM Nagoya Team Shazi, Nagoya Red!
Hello again, kettle, and thank you for joining us today!
This time, I'd like to answer the questions that were asked on the Kikan and Idol's Twitter page in advance.
Thank you for all the questions!
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of questions you have in store for me!
I will definitely protect this one thing. You'll protect it?
Hee... I will. I'll protect it. What's this?
It's loose, but the limit is 3 ice creams a day.
No more than three ice creams a day. This is a promise I made to my parents.
For some reason, it's even in the lyrics of the song Hello!
I'm not sure why, but it is.
In the summer, I eat a lot of ice cream, but I eat breakfast, I eat breakfast. I feel more energetic when I eat breakfast. In the morning, I eat a lot of chocolate and vanilla type foods, which are quite rich, and for lunch, I eat a lot of crisps and Pinot, which are easy to eat.
I eat chocolate even in summer.
I don't know what to do...
Recently, I...
I bought a bomb at 31.
I bought those 12 pieces by myself and left.
12 singles.
And out of them, I really liked...
Cotton candy purple ones.
It has just the right amount of sweetness.
It's a taste that you can't find in regular candy or ice cream.
I like it so much.
Cotton Candy is about number two at the moment.
Third place, I think it was 7?
They came out with a white bear kinako.
I like polar bears the most in the ice cream world.
And then they came out with kinako.
I thought it was a bit of a revolution.
Until now, fruit has been the base of ice cream.
Now you can have kinako too!
Shirokuma, please try it!
I think it's only available for a limited time.
It would be a waste if they run out!
I don't know what to do about the first place!
But I want to eat this in the morning.
Bulgarian Ice Cream Blueberry is now available.
I wonder if it will be limited time only.
Bulgarian ice cream is often eaten by people who do strength training.
It's an easy-to-eat ice cream, but it's good for you.
So I can eat it without feeling guilty at all.
I recommend it.
It's delicious, and it tastes great.
Well, I think that if you have something to look forward to, whether it's your work or your personal life, it will motivate you to do your best, and when you're done, you can do this.
Right now, I'm looking forward to playing Zelda.
Not the current Zelda, but the previous one, Brace of Wilds, I think it's called. I'm playing Brace of Wilds, which is the last Zelda game, and it's a lot of fun.
It's the first Zelda series I've ever played that I'm allowed to play so freely, and it's definitely better to play them in this order, but I'm taking these weird detours.
It's fun, so that's my motivation now. Find something to do for fun.
Read the Baki series?
That's an unbelievable amount of work.
Baki, Hammer Baki, Grappler Baki...
And there's like 30 volumes of each!
You know, it's impossible.
I watched JoJo when I had a big break.
And JoJo was a lot of minutes long, so it was hard, but it was more than that.
If I could take a week off, I could read Baki.
If I can take a week off, I'll read Baki!
There's an interesting story by Taizan Five that's serialized in JUMP now
Ichinose family's stay is very interesting...
First of all, in the first episodeFirst of all, in the very first episode
The way it pulls you in and makes you wonder what's going to happen next.
The first episode is too good, so I want you to read it from there.
It's kind of dark.
It's a bit difficult to explain the story.
It's a little difficult to explain the story.
When I woke up, I was in a dream.
When I woke up, was it still a dream?
Is it real? A dream? Which is it? I don't know.
It's kind of confusing, isn't it?
The reader doesn't know, and he/she doesn't know either.
That's what tickles me.
I read it hoping that it was a dream.
It was the first time for me to do that.
It's written by a current teacher of Tacopee.
If you're interested in it, please read it!
It's in JUMP.
Hmm...
Country? Country? Where should I go?
I want to go to Asia, but I want to go to France!
I really wanted to go to France at least once.
That's why I majored in French as a second language at the university.
I want to go there at least once!
I want to go there! Please do something!
Live in France!
I have a very positive personality.
I forget most things when I sleep.
This is for better or worse.
Positive.
I don't dwell on things.
What else appeals to you?
People say I have a distinctive voice.
I hope people will remember my voice.
What do you do for your live performances?
What kind of cosmetics do you use?
As I just said, the 2nd EP of team shirts, Awaiting Bear, was released on June 28th!
Yay!
Kenta Matsuguma wrote all the songs for this EP,
Mr. Matsuguma wrote all the songs on this EP, some of which Bushy has heard, and some of which I haven't. I'm so happy to hear this EP! Some of the songs were written by Kenta Matsuguma, and some of them are really cute and catchy songs that Busshi heard,
That is also the point, but there was a cute and catchy song called "Your captive, the ultimate love",
The members asked Mr. Matsuguma to write a song like this at the meeting stage,
The members asked Mr. Matsuguma to write a song about their love for karaage bento.
So the lyrics include words like "Toritori" and "Puripuri," which are all about karaage,
I hope you will listen to the lyrics. There are also many dialogue parts.
Staplerocalism Vol. 3 on Saturday, September 30
Sisters and Immortality! We will be holding the Osaka Takoyaki City version.
Yay!
This one will be held at Gorilla Hall in Osaka, though,
We will be performing with Team Shachi, Igissei and his wife, and Patten Shoujo-tai.
Of course, you can only see them here.
But this is the third time for us to perform this staplerocalism.
This is the third time for me to do this.
The first one was in Taiwan.
The second one was in Taiwan, and the third one was an athletic meet.
And now it's the third time, and I'm very happy that it's going on and on and on and on and on.I'm very happy that it's going on and on and on and on and on!
Please come and visit us!
I was so happy to see that everyone's favorite question was about ice cream or comic books, and I felt that they knew something about me.
Thank you for watching!Thanks again for watching.
That's all for Honoka Akimoto.